<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Valorant Blog</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Valorant Blog</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>VCT 2025 IL Kickoff Trailer</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/kickoff/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/kickoff/</guid>
            <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/YU_1hne0HQc?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;
      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Goldenboy, Pansy, Achilios, and Alan get heated as they debate which region’s VALORANT Champions Tour International League Kickoff is THE must-watch event. Year 5 of the VCT starts NOW. Watch VCT IL Kickoff 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://valorantesports.com/&#34;&gt;https://valorantesports.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tune into the VCT Kickoff tournaments, where 48 teams across 4 leagues head back into the arena to debut huge roster moves and fight for the right to compete at the VCT’s first global event of the 2025 season, Masters Bangkok!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[

    
    <div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
      <iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YU_1hne0HQc?autoplay=0&controls=1&end=0&loop=0&mute=0&start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"
      ></iframe>
    </div>

<p>Goldenboy, Pansy, Achilios, and Alan get heated as they debate which region’s VALORANT Champions Tour International League Kickoff is THE must-watch event. Year 5 of the VCT starts NOW. Watch VCT IL Kickoff 2025 at <a href="https://valorantesports.com/">https://valorantesports.com</a></p>
<p>Tune into the VCT Kickoff tournaments, where 48 teams across 4 leagues head back into the arena to debut huge roster moves and fight for the right to compete at the VCT’s first global event of the 2025 season, Masters Bangkok!</p>
<p>International League Kickoff Start Dates:</p>
<ul>
<li>January 15 - VCT EMEA</li>
<li>January 11 - VCT CN</li>
<li>January 16 - VCT Americas</li>
<li>January 18 - VCT Pacific</li>
</ul>
<p>Follow the VALORANT Champions Tour on social media for more action:</p>
<ul>
<li>Twitter: / valorantesports</li>
<li>Instagram: / valorantesports</li>
<li>Facebook: / valorantesports</li>
<li>TikTok: / valorantesports</li>
<li>Meta Threads: <a href="https://www.threads.net/@valorantesports">https://www.threads.net/@valorantesports</a></li>
<li>WhatsApp: <a href="https://whatsapp.com/channel/0029Vak9">https://whatsapp.com/channel/0029Vak9</a></li>
</ul>
<p>#VALORANTChampionsTour #VALORANT #VCT</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Tejo: Man of Action</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/tejo/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/tejo/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/tejo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our newest initiator, Tejo–the well-dressed man of action–has officially joined our Agent roster.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hailing from Colombia, Tejo will undoubtedly shake up the gameplay with his unique kit that flushes out enemies using a top-down approach. Tejo will require you to think proactively and strategically–analyzing the situation mid-round and using his abilities to help clear the way for your team. Based on the enemy’s playstyle, where are they likely to be? Can you use their location to your advantage and get them in a vulnerable position?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo.png"></p>
<p>Our newest initiator, Tejo–the well-dressed man of action–has officially joined our Agent roster.</p>
<p>Hailing from Colombia, Tejo will undoubtedly shake up the gameplay with his unique kit that flushes out enemies using a top-down approach. Tejo will require you to think proactively and strategically–analyzing the situation mid-round and using his abilities to help clear the way for your team. Based on the enemy’s playstyle, where are they likely to be? Can you use their location to your advantage and get them in a vulnerable position?</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo1.jpg"></p>
<p>“We had a gameplay opportunity where we wanted to have an Initiator who thought of the map a little differently - more top-down instead of taking angles one by one. We wanted to try adding a couple of abilities with outputs like flushing that was really exciting for creating these windows of power,” noted by Ryan “Rycou” Cousart, Game Designer for Tejo.</p>
<p>Initiators need to do things precisely. We’ve all been there–looking up Agent guides on YouTube, heading to a custom to test out a lineup, ghosting through the walls to see if it landed correctly. Tejo offers Initiator players something different by being able to accurately place utility using the map in more precisely targeted areas, instead of relying on the perfect-pixel lineups that some utility with bigger footprints may rely on. This allows you to be more precise with what you want to do but with the trade-off of having a smaller area of impact.</p>
<p>But in order to effectively use his precise utility, Tejo needs some info—and like other Initiators, he&rsquo;s good at gathering that info himself. “Since Tejo can provide information about where the enemies are, it allows him to be a lot more consistent with the value he can bring,” stated John “Riot MEMEMEMEME” Goscicki, Agent Team Lead. “Tejo is one of the few Initiators without a flash so he’ll be more effective with another Initiator like Breach or KAY/O where you can create these really fast, explosive takes.”</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo2.jpg"></p>
<p>Stealth Drone</p>
<p>“Drones typically give a lot of baseline value of information gathering, but we wanted to give this drone a little spin where the information is secondary, and the effect of suppressing an enemy is why you take this drone over others,” Cousart noted.</p>
<p>Whether your team is attacking and attempting to take a site or defending and playing retake, having a drone can be extremely impactful. Especially on maps where there are a lot of corners to clear, it allows your team to take space safely or be prepared to fight for that space. Since drones are great pieces of utility, the enemy team is often prepared to shoot down whatever you’re using to take space. Tejo’s Stealth Drone is unique in that it’s invisible at long range, giving you more time to grab information about where the enemy team could be.</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo3.jpg"></p>
<p>Guided Salvo</p>
<p>When we asked the devs, “Why rockets?”, Cousart smiled and said, “Because rockets are sweet.”</p>
<p>In addition to rockets being sweet, they made sense thematically for what the devs were trying to accomplish.</p>
<p>“When you start putting things like a map targeter or world placements on Agents, you force people to think about the game more proactively and more strategically. We wanted something to lead your team in and show you the effect of telling your team, ‘hey something is going to happen.’ We could’ve used anything but we landed on rockets for these reasons,” Cousart added.</p>
<p>Tejo’s abilities, which revolve around flushing out enemies, consist of 3 outputs: information gathering, damage, and concuss effects. “There’s a lot to consider and be careful about when deciding the output of an ability. Damage as an output is a lot more permanent than a concuss or a flash. It’s worthwhile to explore though and I think we’ve landed in a pretty good spot but that’s one we’ll need to keep a really sharp eye,” stated Ryan “Rycou” Cousart.</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo4.jpg"></p>
<p>Special Delivery</p>
<p>“With how naturally ‘guns down’ the other abilities are, Tejo really needed something that was just simple to understand and simple to cast but still captured that feeling of being explosive but directed. I wanted Special Delivery to be a quick, like, ‘Let’s fight’ button”, stated Cousart.</p>
<p>Unlike the other abilities where Tejo needs time to set up the play, Special Delivery allows him to initiate a fight quickly in the moment. Whether or not an enemy is there for the concuss, using the ability there will give them the confidence they need to take that space. One thing is for certain–even if players can use the ability quickly, we won’t be surprised when players are making fancy lineups to get that perfect angle to land on that perfect circle.</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo5.jpg"></p>
<p>Armageddon</p>
<p>“The rockets are really only valuable if you&rsquo;re following up on the pressure that&rsquo;s created. But the sweet spot is when you fire your rockets and you force people to move and then while they&rsquo;re moving, you&rsquo;re able to capitalize on them having to reposition. Another Agent Tejo would be great with are those who can go in very fast like Neon who can capitalize on the distance he casts his abilities from,” Goscicki noted.</p>
<p>Tejo’s ult, Armageddon, is something enemies will need to be aware of round-to-round. Watch that scoreboard and check how many ult points he’s away from being able to use it since it can heavily impact the flow of a round. The wave of explosions will force enemies to move in a direction of Tejo’s choosing or at least have players moving further back to play retake since the site will be difficult to hold. This will give his team the perfect opportunity to follow up and take control of the space he just created.</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo6.jpg"></p>
<p>The Look, the Attitude, the Skill</p>
<p>So how did Tejo’s gameplay and abilities tie into his character design? The idea of this Agent being an Initiator who can lead a team with strong game sense goes along with the perception of someone that is experienced–experienced in the battlefield and experienced in life.</p>
<p>“The phrase we used a lot was just ‘man of action.’ We’ve all seen the movies, read the books where you just see the dude in the button-up, in the blazer just coming and destroying everyone,” noted Goscicki. “He’s the rugged professional–his shirt is unbuttoned and he’s ready for action. He’s not like Chamber where every detail about his attire matters where it needed to reinforce the idea of landing the perfect shot. Tejo is going to run in there through all the explosions and everything’s got to be loose, wavy, and comfortable.”</p>
<p>Adding onto Tejo’s style, he has fashionable sunglasses that are actually a digital screen that he uses for his abilities. When he uses his Stealth Drone, he sees from the eyes of the drone with his high tech sunglasses. When he pulls out his abilities, he sees through an alternate reality digital readout where he could see all the terrain in front of him at different elevation levels. This is how Tejo can place his abilities at a higher accuracy.</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/tejo7.jpg"></p>
<p>Speaks with Ingrained Confidence</p>
<p>Narrative Writer Ryan “Pwam” Clements stated “When searching for the voice actor who would play one of our agents, it’s important to have a clear understanding of the character in order to find the right voice. So the first step is ensuring that we have the pillars of his personality. These become the razors by which we assess an auditioning actor; not only for their dramatic ability, but can their performance channel those persona pillars in a believable way?”</p>
<p>Prior to casting Tejo’s voice actor, Clements put together a casting sheet with the following notes: “Tejo speaks with ingrained confidence developed from decades of difficult, dangerous assignments. It’s the kind of confidence that saturates every word, leaving no room for questioning. He is professional; he describes things as they are, matter-of-fact, precise, and measured. An equally intense man, Tejo looks people in the eyes when he speaks and when he listens, his voice unfaltering.”</p>
<p>Everything about Tejo from his abilities to his appearance and more are elements of a strong leader. If you play Tejo, your teammates will rely on you to create opportunities for them to take space. Everyone can play Tejo but those with strategic game sense who can step up to being a leader will make him really shine on the battlefield.</p>
<p>As Tejo would say, “We can stand around all day talking about killing them&hellip; or we just do it.,” so let’s hop into a game.</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Introducing the 2025 VCT Team Capsules</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/capsule/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/capsule/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Image Description&#34; src=&#34;//localhost:1313/images/capsule.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;An Expansion on our Commitment to Fandom and the Future of Esports
Today, we’re excited to announce the 2025 VCT Team Capsules, which build on the success of last year to offer you more ways to represent your favorite teams while directly contributing to their future. Team Capsules will allow fans to support their favorite teams directly, with a portion of proceeds going to the organizations throughout the season.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/capsule.png"></p>
<p>An Expansion on our Commitment to Fandom and the Future of Esports
Today, we’re excited to announce the 2025 VCT Team Capsules, which build on the success of last year to offer you more ways to represent your favorite teams while directly contributing to their future. Team Capsules will allow fans to support their favorite teams directly, with a portion of proceeds going to the organizations throughout the season.</p>
<p>Last year, you showed incredible support, helping us share over $44 million USD with our partnered teams from the Champions Collection and Team Skins. Your passion fuels this scene, and with the 2025 Capsules, we’re excited to build on last year’s team capsules with a new playcard with premium glow, new skin features, and new designs!</p>
<p>Esports Digital Goods: What’s New?
Our goal with esports cosmetics remains the same: give players a way to show their pride in-game while financially supporting teams. In 2025, we’re building on last year’s momentum by introducing new digital offerings:</p>
<p>Returning Favorites: The Team Capsules and Champions Collection are back.
Season Capsule: A new collection featuring a unique melee skin, inspired by the success of the LOCK//IN collection in 2023. We’ll be sharing more information on this capsule later in the year.</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/capsule2.jpg"></p>
<p>Why the Classic?
The Classic is synonymous with VALORANT—it’s your trusty sidearm which is featured in every round of VALORANT, giving it extended time in the spotlight. Like a team jersey, it’s always in play, making it the perfect canvas for fans to showcase their loyalty.</p>
<p>For 2025, the Team Capsules were designed with a “Midnight Splash” theme, in combination with a new set of branding from each of our partner teams, to create an “alternate jersey” to 2024. The goal here was to give a unique feel and identity to the Classics in 2025, and provide VCT teams with a platform to express their brand creativity in new ways.</p>
<p>What’s in the 2025 Capsules?</p>
<p>Here’s what you can expect in each Team Capsule:</p>
<p>Upgraded Classic Skin with team-themed design and new branding elements.
Achievement Tracker Inspect for teams with the accolades of major victories.
2025 Player Card with a premium finish, showcasing team identity and creativity.
Original 2024 Spray and Gun Buddy, with discounts for returning owners.
Classics representing teams who have won major events will feature special “winner’s flair,” like EDG for their victories at VCT CN and 2024 Champions!</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/capsule3.jpg"></p>
<p>The EDG player card will also feature Champion’s flair, unique to the 2024 World Champions!</p>
<p>When Can You Grab Them?
The 2025 Team Capsules will be available throughout the season in the in-game Esports Store. Returning players will receive effective discounts for previously owned items, making it easier than ever to rep your fandom. Capsules for teams who earned promotion via Ascension, as well as Boom Esports, will be released later in the season.</p>
<p>We’re hyped to see which teams you’ll be rooting for as we head into the next season of the VCT!</p>
<p><img alt="Image Description" src="/images/capsule4.jpg"></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Welcome to Season 2025</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/season/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/season/</guid>
            <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q1HgRPb_5NI?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;
      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Studio Head, Anna Donlon, stops by to share some feels as VALORANT heads into its 5th year—a time for reflection, evolution, and dedication to all of you. Welcome to Season 2025. GL HF.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow the VALORANT Champions Tour on social media for more action:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter: / valorantesports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instagram: / valorantesports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facebook: / valorantesports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;TikTok: / valorantesports&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meta Threads: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.threads.net/@valorantesports&#34;&gt;https://www.threads.net/@valorantesports&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;WhatsApp: &lt;a href=&#34;https://whatsapp.com/channel/0029Vak9&#34;&gt;https://whatsapp.com/channel/0029Vak9&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#VALORANTChampionsTour #VALORANT #VCT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[

    
    <div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
      <iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q1HgRPb_5NI?autoplay=0&controls=1&end=0&loop=0&mute=0&start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"
      ></iframe>
    </div>

<p>Studio Head, Anna Donlon, stops by to share some feels as VALORANT heads into its 5th year—a time for reflection, evolution, and dedication to all of you. Welcome to Season 2025. GL HF.</p>
<p>Follow the VALORANT Champions Tour on social media for more action:</p>
<ul>
<li>Twitter: / valorantesports</li>
<li>Instagram: / valorantesports</li>
<li>Facebook: / valorantesports</li>
<li>TikTok: / valorantesports</li>
<li>Meta Threads: <a href="https://www.threads.net/@valorantesports">https://www.threads.net/@valorantesports</a></li>
<li>WhatsApp: <a href="https://whatsapp.com/channel/0029Vak9">https://whatsapp.com/channel/0029Vak9</a></li>
</ul>
<p>#VALORANTChampionsTour #VALORANT #VCT</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>What’s New for Season 2025 // Dev Updates</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/new/</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/new/</guid>
            <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/YpNsGFd74fk?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;
      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy and the dev team are here to welcome you to a new year of VALORANT—VAL’s 5th year! Watch to find out what the devs are cooking up in their areas of the game for the start of 2025 and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And if you haven’t watched Anna’s latest video, Welcome to Season 2025, you can check it out here:    • Welcome to Season 2025 - VALORANT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[

    
    <div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
      <iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YpNsGFd74fk?autoplay=0&controls=1&end=0&loop=0&mute=0&start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"
      ></iframe>
    </div>

<p>Andy and the dev team are here to welcome you to a new year of VALORANT—VAL’s 5th year! Watch to find out what the devs are cooking up in their areas of the game for the start of 2025 and beyond.</p>
<p>And if you haven’t watched Anna’s latest video, Welcome to Season 2025, you can check it out here:    • Welcome to Season 2025 - VALORANT</p>
<p>Executive Producer: Andy Ho
Agents Lead: John Goscicki
Game Designer: Ryan Cousart
Product Manager: Tiffy Tsay
Live Design Balance Lead: Dan Hardison
Product Lead, Expressions: Preeti Pinto
Art Director: Sean Marino
Product Lead, Competitive Systems: Stephen Kraman
Product Engineering Lead: Marcus Reid
Global Head of VALORANT Esports: Leo Faria</p>
<p>Recorded on October 29, 2024</p>
<p>Timestamps:
Intro: 00:00
Agents: 01:10
Gameplay and Live Balance: 03:58
Premium Content: 06:57
Competitive and Ranked: 09:14
Player Behavior: 10:39
Replays: 12:05
Esports: 14:50
Outro: 17:49</p>
<p>—</p>
<p>Play VALORANT: <a href="https://riot.com/3idlntG">https://riot.com/3idlntG</a></p>
<p>Join the Discord server: <a href="https://riot.com/3n1xltZ">https://riot.com/3n1xltZ</a></p>
<p>Follow us:
Twitter: <a href="https://riot.com/2HIv1s1">https://riot.com/2HIv1s1</a></p>
<p>Instagram: <a href="https://riot.com/2S8uTnm">https://riot.com/2S8uTnm</a></p>
<p>TikTok: <a href="https://riot.com/3FwNKSE">https://riot.com/3FwNKSE</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>RE:FUEL // ARAXYS Skin Reveal Trailer</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/araxys/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/araxys/</guid>
            <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/vdfexNscpPo?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;
      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refuel your arsenal with the new additions to the Araxys skinline.
Featuring the Phantom, Outlaw, Guardian, Sheriff and the Bio-Atomizers. Bundle drops in the shop on December 12th.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Play VALORANT: &lt;a href=&#34;https://riot.com/3idlntG&#34;&gt;https://riot.com/3idlntG&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Follow us:
Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://riot.com/2HIv1s1&#34;&gt;https://riot.com/2HIv1s1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Instagram: &lt;a href=&#34;https://riot.com/2S8uTnm&#34;&gt;https://riot.com/2S8uTnm&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TikTok: &lt;a href=&#34;https://riot.com/3FwNKSE&#34;&gt;https://riot.com/3FwNKSE&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[

    
    <div style="position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;">
      <iframe allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen" loading="eager" referrerpolicy="strict-origin-when-cross-origin" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/vdfexNscpPo?autoplay=0&controls=1&end=0&loop=0&mute=0&start=0" style="position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;" title="YouTube video"
      ></iframe>
    </div>

<p>Refuel your arsenal with the new additions to the Araxys skinline.
Featuring the Phantom, Outlaw, Guardian, Sheriff and the Bio-Atomizers. Bundle drops in the shop on December 12th.</p>
<p>Play VALORANT: <a href="https://riot.com/3idlntG">https://riot.com/3idlntG</a></p>
<p>Follow us:
Twitter: <a href="https://riot.com/2HIv1s1">https://riot.com/2HIv1s1</a></p>
<p>Instagram: <a href="https://riot.com/2S8uTnm">https://riot.com/2S8uTnm</a></p>
<p>TikTok: <a href="https://riot.com/3FwNKSE">https://riot.com/3FwNKSE</a></p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
